12/11/2018 Your Resume



■ BOJANMADZARACKA@GMAIL.COM
□ 091/755-4977

Date: 11 December 2018

I am a young programmer in the making. The amount of my experience is within my own personal projects. Some of them are simple learning projects that will never be deployed, while others are more advanced projects in the domain of Web development and design.

I am well versed in procedural and object oriented programming, MVC architecture, and test driven development. Although my main focus for the time being is server-side development, necessity has driven me to learn javascript, CSS and HTML5 as well as some more advanced technologies like Vue 2 and SASS, which I do plan on mastering as well. For the last several months i have been working as s Software developer in a firm that deals with large scale productions over several plants and within several countries. The application was meant to be a simple production planning application, however through time it evolved and now covers every nook and cranny of a ginormous production system. Though my time in active programming might seem short I assure you that I have more than compensated for that in concentrating most of my free time and focus into learning and mastering what I found to be the one unchanging thing throughout my life, my love and interest in programming.

Which brings me to the reason for my wish to work with you and your team. The scope of the project at hand and its never ending need for improvement makes it the perfect environment for me. The chance to learn from such a big project and improve myself is too great to pass by, so I am sure that if you take a chance and give me one to prove myself, you will not be disappointed and will find out that I can be an ever-improving asset to both you and your project.

I look forward to hearing from You or one of Your team.

12/11/2018 Your Resume

Bojan Madžarac

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a self-taught programmer that has spent most of his life dabbling in code. At an age of 26 I have decided to dig deeper in software development and have since spent almost all of my free time writing code. From smaller procedural scripts to larger MVC based web pages to even bigger and more demanding projects realized through Domain Driven Design. How the scope of my ambitions grew so did my skills and methods, from a beginner writing code in c++ through my first solo hobby-project of making a landing page in php, html5 and css to my latest project where I use Laravel, Vue.js and SASS to create a fully responsive Web app. Afterwards i have mostly moved to the Smyfony 4 framework, however i still use both depending on the circumstances.

I vigorously seek out knowledge, new technologies and techniques to improve myself. What I lack in experience I will more than make up with my ability and will to learn and improve. I wholeheartedly believe that those that meet and talk to me will see my potential and will not be disappointed in my work and effort.

EXPERIENCE

WAITER

*Narca, Varaždin, 2010-2011*Worked as a waiter through collage years

WAITER

Lavra, Varaždin, 2012-2013 Worked as a waiter

SALES AGENT

Vip d.o.o, Zagreb, 2013-2014

Worked as a sales agent in a telecommunication company

BARMAN

Moja Diridika - Papas bar, Karlovac, 2014-2015 Worked as a barman/barkeep

WAREHOUSE WORKER

*Kaufland d.o.o, Jastrebarsko, 2015-2016*Warehouse worker - packaging and shipment

KEY-USER IN TRAINING

Boxmark Leather d.o.o., Varaždin, 11.01.2016. - 11.01.2017

Managed daily SAP interactions and inventory lists, as well as handled potential problems in production related to SAP and PPA systems

INCOMING MATERIAL QUALITY INSPECTOR

Boxmark Leather d.o.o., Varaždin, 11.01.2017. - now

Managed incoming material certificates and suppliers as well as handled any potential problems they might cause.

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Boxmark d.o.o., Varaždin, 01.10.2018 - now

A Software developer on a large scale Production Planing Application, that spans 8 production sites.

PROJECTS

MULTIPURPOSE FORUM TEMPLATE

Currently developing a multipurpose web template as a plugin for primarily the Web Blog in production, but will be usable as a standalone page. Development is being done in Laravel and Vue

MULTIPURPOSE WEB BLOG TEMPLATE

Currently developing a multipurpose blog template with a custom CMS. The project was originally started in vanilla PHP with javascript but due to complexity and the future ease of

12/11/2018 Your Resume

scalability was stoped and is being remade in Laravel and Vue.

OAUTH2 AUTHENTICATION AND AUTHORIZATION

An Oauth2 security delegation system for a microservices app

PRODUCTION PLANING APPLICATION

A production planing application realized through DDD

EDUCATION COMPUTER TECHNICIAN

Tehnička škola Karlovac • Karlovac, Croatia • 2009

SKILLS PHP OOP MVC PROGRAMMING ARCHITECTURE WEB DEVELOPMENT

LARAVELJAVASCRIPTVUE.JSTEST DRIVEN DEVELOPMENTPHPUNITSQLHTML5CSSXMLC++AJAXMICROSOFT OFFICEGITHUB

XAMPP WAMPP DATA MANAGEMENT WEB DESIGN SYMFONY 4

DOCTRINE GIT **DOCTRINE** DOMAIN DRIVEN DESIGNE **JQUERY** AJAX

OAUTH2

CONTACT ■ BOJANMADZARACKA@GMAIL.COM

091/755-4977

The HTTPS://WWW.LINKEDIN.COM/IN/BOJAN-MADŽARAC-8B7929B3/